selectpayment.com 2006-02-06

# Privacy Statement

Select Payment takes privacy and data protection issues very seriously. Select Payment Privacy Policy is designed to ensure the safety of personal identity information collected from merchants who sign up for Select Payment electronic check or check conversion services and submit information through the Internet. 

As the Select Payment services change, we may revise this policy. If you have questions about Select Payment privacy practices please contact us at support@selectpayment.com. 

Select Payment Privacy Policy covers the handling of personal information collected from merchants who use the Select Payment electronic check processing solution, as well as consumer information that we acquire in the course of our business. This Policy also covers the handling of personal information that Select Payment business partners may share with it. 

**Information Collected**   
Select Payment collects personal information when you register for a merchant account. Select Payment may also receive personal information from its resellers and other business partners. 

When you sign up with Select Payment, we ask for your contact information (such as your name, street address, phone, fax and email address), and may request information pertaining to your business, such as a financial statements, bank account and/or settlement account information. 

In processing an electronic check transaction, we typically receive from the merchant information related to the transaction. This includes information about the transaction that a consumer has furnished the merchant in placing the order. 

The personal information we receive in processing transactions varies according to the nature of the transaction and the way in which merchants are using our electronic check services. It will include customer information, banking information and transaction information. 

Select Payment uses the information collected to fulfill merchant requests for e-check services, to process e-check transactions, to facilitate billing, and otherwise deliver the Internet payment gateway services. Personal consumer information is used to process payment transactions and for no other purpose. 

**Information Disclosure**   
Protecting personal information about merchants and consumers is an important part of our business. Personal information is shared with third party banks to the extent necessary for Select Payment to complete the e-check transaction. 

We also may release personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law or verify information with other companies for fraud protection and risk reduction. 

**Information Security**   
Information security is critical to our business. We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using 128-bit Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you send. Information gathered is stored on computers located in a secure data center. The number of people at the data center that have physical access to these computers is limited. Firewalls and other security technology are used to prevent system computers from being accessed by unauthorized persons. 

It is the merchant's responsibility to protect against unauthorized access to the Login ID/password. Be sure to sign off when finished with a merchant session and protect the password used to access the Select Payment web site. 

**System Access**   
Select Payment gives merchant authorized personnel the ability to set system access and user permissions on an individual basis. The merchant may determine system view administrative settings.
